Finding Aid for the Slee Lecture Recital Recordings, 1957-1975
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 44, November 16, 1964, 1964-11-16, 4 7 inch reels; Butler Auditorium, Capen Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_044_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_044_02_01.wav, ubmu0062_044_03_01.wav, ubmu0062_044_04_01.wav (Box 2, Reel 025-028)
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 236
  Haieff, Alexei, 1914-1994
  Lecture: Musical education and the new musical styles (a speculation)
  Performers: Alexei Haieff, lecturer
  Note: Program inserted
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 237
  Sonata, violoncello, piano (1963)
  Performers: Jay Humeston, violoncello; Emmanuel Sinderbrand, piano
  Duration: 14:37
  Note: Program inserted indicates the work is possibly on this reel. If not, it is probably on Reel 26
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 238
  Sonata, pianos 2 (1953)
  Performers: Arthur Gold, Robert Fizdale, pianos
  Duration: 19:35
  Note: Program contents not specified on container; title of work from program inserted in Reel 25.
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 239
  Sonata, piano, 4 hands (1918)
  Performers: Arthur Gold, Robert Fizdale, piano duo
  Duration: 5:36
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 240
  Elegie (en accords alternes) (1959)
  Duration: 5:33
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_06
  Original cassette number: SLR 241
  Capriccio (d'apres Le bal masque) (1952)
  Duration: 4:11
  Work number: ubmu0062_044_07
  Original cassette number: SLR 242
  L'embarquement pour Cythere (1951)
  Note: Program contents not specified on container; title of work from cassette catalog - it is not on the program in Reel 25.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 45, December 18, 1964, 1964-12-18, 3 7 inch reels; Butler Auditorium, Capen Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_045_01.wav, ubmu0062_045_02.wav, ubmu0062_045_03.wav, ubmu0062_045_04.wav (Box 3, Reel 029-031)
  Work number: ubmu0062_045_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 246
  Three bagatelles
  Performers: Sylvia Marlowe, harpsichord
  Duration: 6:20
  Work number: ubmu0062_045_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 247
  Carter, Elliott, 1908-
  Sonata, harpsichord, flute, oboe, violoncello (1952)
  Performers: Samuel Baron, flute; Ronald Roseman, oboe; Alexander Kouguell. violoncello; Sylvia Marlowe, harpsichord
  Duration: 16:01
  Work number: ubmu0062_045_06
  Original cassette number: SLR 248
  Falla, Manuel de, 1876-1946
  Concerto, harpsichord
  Performers: Sylvia Marlowe, harpsichord; Samuel Baron, flute; Ronald Roseman, oboe; David Glazer, clarinet; Matthew Raimond, violin; Alexander Kouguell, violoncello
  Duration: 14:09
  Work number: ubmu0062_045_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 243
  Lecture: Dangerous disparities
  Note: Program inserted in container
  Work number: ubmu0062_045_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 244
  Lovers - A narrative in ten scenes (1964)
  Performers: Sylvia Marlowe, harpsichord; Ronald Roseman, oboe, English horn; Alexander Kouguell, violoncello; John Bergamo, percussion
  Duration: 18:30
  Note: Premiere performance; Program contents not specified on containers (1-4). Program inserted in Reel 29 indicates a different order for the pieces on the concert. Check content against program.
  Work number: ubmu0062_045_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 245
  Sauguet, Henri, 1901-1989
  Suite royale (1962)
  Duration: 14:25
  Note: U.S. premiere
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 46, February 22, 1965, 1965-02-22, 4 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_046_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_046_01_02.wav, ubmu0062_046_03.wav, ubmu0062_046_04.wav (Box 3, Reel 033-36)
  Work number: ubmu0062_046_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 249
  Kagel, Mauricio
  Lecture: On new electronic and instrumental music
  Performers: Mauricio Kagel, lecturer
  Note: Program inserted in container. Reel 33 is marked as "1 of 2"; Reel 34 is marked "2 of 2" but also indicates it is "copy of 15"" which could refer to Reel 35 - check for duplicate content.
  Work number: ubmu0062_046_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 251
  Sonant
  Performers: Stanley Silverman, Spanish and electric guitars; Buell Neidlinger, double bass; John Bergamo, Jan Williams, percussion
  Duration: 10:35
  Note: Reel 35 is possibly recorded at 15 ips - it is marked "15". Content of both reels is not certain - check for content. The work Sonant could be on Reel 33 or 34, too.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 47, March 24, 1965, 1965-03-24, 4 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_047_01.wav, ubmu0062_047_02.wav, ubmu0062_047_03.wav, ubmu0062_047_04.wav (Box 3, Reel 037-040)
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 255
  Sextet, 2 violins, 2 violas, 2 violoncellos (1953)
  Performers: Paul Zukofsky, Rivka Mandelkern, violins; Jean Dupouy, Inti Marshall, violas; Jay Humeston, Howard Colf, violoncellos
  Duration: 8:37
  Note: U.S. premiere; Reel 39 marked "3 of 4"; reel 40 marked "4 of 4"
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_07
  Original cassette number: SLR 256C
  Metapiece (Mimetics)(1961)
  Performers: Tape played: Mauricio Kagel, piano
  Duration: 8:32
  Note: U.S. premiere. Performed simultaneously with Mimetics and Sextet. Reel 39 marked "3 of 4"; reel 40 marked "4 of 4"
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 256A
  Mimetics (Metapiece)(1961)
  Performers: Fredric Myrow, piano
  Note: Performed simultaneously with Sextet and Metapiece. Reel 39 marked "3 of 4"; reel 40 marked "4 of 4"
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 254
  Metapiece (Mimetics) (1961)
  Duration: 18:32
  Note: Reel 39 marked "3 of 4"; reel 40 marked "4 of 4"
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 253
  Anagrama (1957-58)
  Performers: Tape played
  Duration: 18:33
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 252
  Lecture: About certain relationships between language and musical composition
  Note: Program inserted. Reel 37 is marked "1 of 4"; Reel 38 is marked "2 of 4"
  Work number: ubmu0062_047_06
  Original cassette number: SLR 256B
  Note: Performed simultaneously with Mimetics and Metapiece. Reel 39 marked "3 of 4"; reel 40 marked "4 of 4"
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 48, April 3, 1965, 1965-04-03, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_048_01.wav, ubmu0062_048_02.wav (Box 4, Reel 041-042)
  Work number: ubmu0062_048_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 257
  Lecture: About the musical theatre
  Note: Reel 41 is marked on container spine as ½; Reel 42 is marked 2/2. But Reel 41 container is also marked Pandora's box and Reel 42 Lecture. Check content and reverse order if necessary.
  Work number: ubmu0062_048_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 258
  Antithese (1962)
  Note: Tape recording realized at the Siemens Studio for Electronic Music, Munich
  Work number: ubmu0062_048_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 259
  Pandorasbox (1964)
  Performers: David Tudor, bandoneon
  Duration: 22:16
  Note: U.S. premiere; Reel 41 is marked "Pandora's Box" but is also marked ½ so the content and order is not clear.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 49, October 11, 1965, 1965-10-11, 1 7 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_049_01.wav, ubmu0062_049_02.wav (Box 4, Reel 043)
  Work number: ubmu0062_049_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 261
  Lecture: Music and language
  Note: "Head out; use left channel"
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 50, December 13, 1965, 1965-12-13, 2 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_050_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_050_01_02.wav, ubmu0062_050_02.wav (Box 4, Reel 044-045)
  Work number: ubmu0062_050_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 263
  Berio, Luciano, 1925-2003
  Circles (1960)
  Duration: 18:29
  Note: Reel 44 marked 1 of 2; Reel 45 marked 2 of 2; contents not marked on containers: title of work from cassette catalog
  Work number: ubmu0062_050_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 262
  Lecture: A few aspects of vocal music
  Performers: Luciano Berio, lecturer
  Note: Reel 44 marked 1 of 2; Reel 45 marked 2 of 2; contents not marked on containers
  Work number: ubmu0062_050_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 264
  Laborintus II (1965). Excerpt
  Duration: 21:13
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 51, December 16, 1965, 1965-12-16, 2 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_051_01.wav, ubmu0062_051_02.wav (Box 4, Reel 046-047)
  Work number: ubmu0062_051_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 268
  Concerto for celesta and harpsichord soli
  Performers: Daniel Pinkham, celesta; Helen Keaney, harpsichord
  Duration: 9:27
  Note: Reel 46 marked 1 of 2; Reel 47 marked 2 of 2; contents not marked on containers: title of work from cassette catalog
  Work number: ubmu0062_051_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 269
  Song of Jephthah's daughter
  Performers: Barbara Wallace, soprano; Daniel Pinkham, piano
  Duration: 12:25
  Work number: ubmu0062_051_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 265
  Lecture: A twelve-tone approach to tonal vocal music
  Performers: Daniel Pinkham, lecturer
  Note: Reel 46 marked 1 of 2; Reel 47 marked 2 of 2; contents not marked on containers. Cassette catalog marked "Second part of lecture missing (not recorded? /erased?)"
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 52, February 28, 1966, 1966-02-28, 4 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_052_01.wav, ubmu0062_052_02.wav, ubmu0062_052_03.wav, ubmu0062_052_04.wav (Box 4, Reel 048-051)
  Work number: ubmu0062_052_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 274
  Pousseur, Henri
  Trois visages de Liege (1961)
  Duration: 20:31
  Note: Tape realized at SME, Brussels. Reels marked 1 of 4 through 4 of 4 with no indication of contents on each reel. Title of work from cassette catalog
  Work number: ubmu0062_052_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 272
  Rimes pour differentes sources sonores (1958-59). Part II
  Duration: 9:14
  Note: Tape realized by the composer at SME, Brussels. Reels marked 1 of 4 through 4 of 4 with no indication of contents on each reel. Title of work from cassette catalog
  Work number: ubmu0062_052_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 271
  Scambi (1957)
  Duration: 6:27
  Note: Tape realized by the composer at RAI, Milan. Reels marked 1 of 4 through 4 of 4 with no indication of contents on each reel. Title of work from cassette catalog
  Work number: ubmu0062_052_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 270
  Lecture: Calculation and imagination in electronic music
  Performers: Henri Pousseur, lecturer
  Note: Reels marked 1 of 4 through 4 of 4 with no indication of contents on each reel. "Half tk. Mono. L ch. Only"
  Work number: ubmu0062_052_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 273
  Electre (1960). Excerpt
  Duration: 8:08
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 53, March 14, 1966, 1966-03-14, 4 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_053_01.wav, ubmu0062_053_02.wav, ubmu0062_053_03.wav, ubmu0062_053_04.wav (Box 4, Reel 052-055)
  Work number: ubmu0062_053_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 276
  Miroir de Votre Faust
  Performers: Sylvia Brigham-Dimiziani, soprano; Frederic Rzewski, piano
  Duration: 29:31
  Note: Program inserted in Reel 52. Reels marked 1 of 4 through 4 of 4. Specific content not noted. Title of work from cassette catalog and program
  Work number: ubmu0062_053_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 275
  Lecture: Harmony, a renewed question
  Performers: Henri Pousseur, lecturer; Frederic Rzewski, piano
  Note: Program inserted in Reel 52. Reels marked 1 of 4 through 4 of 4. Specific content not noted.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 54, May 2, 1966, 1966-05-02, 3 7 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_054_01.wav, ubmu0062_054_02.wav, ubmu0062_054_03.wav (Box 4, Reel 056-058)
  Work number: ubmu0062_054_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 277
  Lecture: Webern and silence
  Note: Reels marked 1 of 3 through 3 of 3. Program inserted in Reel 56. Contents of each reel not specified.
  Work number: ubmu0062_054_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 278
  Funf Satze, op. 5
  Performers: Lasalle Quartet: Walter Levin, Henry Meyer, violins; Peter Kamnitzer, viola; Jack Kirstein, violoncello
  Duration: 11:34
  Note: Reels marked 1 of 3 through 3 of 3. Program inserted in Reel 56. Contents of each reel not specified. Title of work from program
  Work number: ubmu0062_054_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 279
  Bagatelles, string, op.9
  Duration: 4:20
  Work number: ubmu0062_054_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 280
  Quartet, strings, op. 28
  Performers: Lasalle Quartet: Walter Levin, Henry Meyer, violins, Peter Kamnitzer, viola; Jack Kirstein, violoncello
  Duration: 8:50
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 55, October 15, 1966, 1966-10-15, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_055_01.wav, ubmu0062_055_02.wav (Box 5, Reel 059-060)
  Work number: ubmu0062_055_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 284
  Sequenza III (1966)
  Performers: Cathy Berberian, soprano
  Duration: 8:41
  Note: On hub with no reel. Reel 1 of 2 through reel 2 of 2 with contents on each reel not specified. Title of work from cassette catalog
  Work number: ubmu0062_055_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 283
  Bussotti, Sylvano
  Torso (Letture di Braibanti) (1960-63)
  Duration: 4:06
  Work number: ubmu0062_055_06
  Original cassette number: SLR 285
  Berberian, Cathy
  Stripsody (1966)
  Duration: 4:43
  Work number: ubmu0062_055_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 282A
  Cage, John
  Aria (performed simultaneously with the following work)
  Work number: ubmu0062_055_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 281
  Lecture: Chance in new music [part I]
  Note: On hub with no reel. Reel 1 of 2 through reel 2 of 2 with contents on each reel not specified
  Work number: ubmu0062_055_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 282B
  Fontana mix (performed simultaneously with the preceding work)
  Note: Tape realized by the composer; On hub with no reel. Reel 1 of 2 through reel 2 of 2 with contents on each reel not specified. Title of work from cassette catalog
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 56, November 21, 1966, 1966-11-21, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_056_01.wav, ubmu0062_056_02_01.wav, ubmu0062_056_02_02.wav (Box 5, Reel 061-062)
  Work number: ubmu0062_056_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 286
  Lecture: Chance in new music [part II]
  Note: Reels marked 1 of 2 and 2 of 2; program inserted in both reels. On back of reel 062: "What is this tape? (certainly not "Telemusik")." Contains Schumann and Hindemith?? Check contents before reformatting
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 57, December 18, 1966, 1966-12-18, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_057_01.wav, ubmu0062_057_02.wav (Box 5, Reel 063)
  Work number: ubmu0062_057_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 288
  Lecture: Chance in new music [part III]
  Note: Program inserted in container. "Scrap tape" written on the front cover.
  Work number: ubmu0062_057_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 289
  Mumma, Gordon, 1935-
  Horn (1965)
  Performers: Gordon Mumma, horn; Robert Ashley, David Behrman, cybersonic consoles
  Duration: 10:10
  Work number: ubmu0062_057_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 290
  Behrman, David
  Players with circuits (1966)
  Performers: Robert Ashley, zither; Gordon Mumma, piano; David Behrman, Alvin Lucier, circuits
  Duration: 10:00
  Work number: ubmu0062_057_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 291
  Lucier, Alvin
  Mafia (1965)
  Performers: Recording played
  Duration: 11:26
  Work number: ubmu0062_057_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 292
  Ashley, Robert, 1930-
  The wolf man (1964)
  Performers: Robert Ashley, voice
  Duration: 6:45
  Note: Tape realized by the composer. Program inserted in container. "Scrap tape" written on the front cover.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 58, January 23, 1967, 1967-01-23, 2 10 inch reels; Norton Conference Theater Preservation files: ubmu0062_058_01.wav, ubmu0062_058_02.wav (Box 5, Reel 064-065)
  Work number: ubmu0062_058_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 293
  Lecture: Chance in new music [part IV]
  Note: Tapes are marked Slee Lecture ½1/67 2/3 and 3/3 on spine - check content to see if they match the lecture content. Presumably at least one reel is missing.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 59, March 13, 1967, 1967-03-13, 2 10 inch reels; Norton Conference Theater Preservation files: ubmu0062_059_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_059_02_01.wav (Box 5, Reel 066-067)
  Work number: ubmu0062_059_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 294
  Lecture: Chance in new music [part V]
  Performers: Henri Pousseur, lecturer, Carlos Alsina, piano
  Note: Reels marked 1 of 2 and 2 of 2. Program inserted in container of both containers. Content on each reel not specified.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 60, April 10, 1967, 1967-04-10, 2 10 inch reels; Norton Conference Theater Preservation files: ubmu0062_060_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_060_01_02.wav, ubmu0062_060_02.wav (Box 5, Reel 068-069)
  Work number: ubmu0062_060_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 297
  Votre Faust. Excerpt
  Duration: 14:58
  Note: Reels marked 1 of 2 and 2 of 2. Program inserted in container of both containers. Content on each reel not specified. Written on the back of reel 067: "A senior recital, William Courtial, classical guitar-April 1967 Baird Hall." - check content
  Work number: ubmu0062_060_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 295
  Lecture: Chance in new music [part VI]
  Work number: ubmu0062_060_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 296
  Votre Faust. Prologue, The fair, Interlude, Cabaret.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 61, October 11, 1968, 1968-10-11, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_061.wav (Box 6, Reel 070)
  Work number: ubmu0062_061_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 298
  Hiller, Lejaren Arthur, 1924-1994
  Lecture: The composer's uses of modern technology, part I
  Performers: Lejaren Hiller, lecturer
  Note: Container spine labeled ½ so end of program is possibly missing.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 62, November 12, 1968, 1968-11-12, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_062_01.wav, ubmu0062_062_02.wav (Box 6, Reel 071)
  Work number: ubmu0062_062_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 301
  Lecture: The composer's uses of modern technology, part II
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 63, February 7, 1969, 1969-02-07, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_063_01.wav, ubmu0062_063_02.wav (Box 6, Reel 072)
  Work number: ubmu0062_063_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 302
  Lecture: The composer's uses of modern technology, part III
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 64, February 14, 1969, 1969-02-14, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_064.wav (Box 6, Reel 073)
  Work number: ubmu0062_064_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 303
  Transicion II (1958-59)
  Performers: Yuji Takahashi, piano; Jan Williams, percussion
  Duration: 11:59
  Note: Buffalo premiere; Tape realized by the composer. Concert program inserted in container.
  Work number: ubmu0062_064_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 304
  Takahashi, Yuji, 1938-
  Nekuia (1966)
  Performers: Robert Cram, bamboo flute
  Duration: 4:52
  Note: Premiere performance. Concert program inserted in container.
  Work number: ubmu0062_064_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 305
  Brün, Herbert, 1918-2000
  Plot for percussion (1966)
  Performers: Ed Burnham, percussion
  Duration: 5:23
  Note: Buffalo premiere. Concert program inserted in container.
  Work number: ubmu0062_064_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 306
  Grossman, Gary
  Four studies for Illiac II (1965)
  Performers: Lejaren Hiller, projections
  Duration: 0:57
  Note: Buffalo premiere; Recording tapers off at approx. 57 and rest of tape is blank; Tape realized by the composer. Concert program inserted in container.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 65, March 3, 1969, 1969-03-03, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_065_01.wav, ubmu0062_065_02.wav (Box 6, Reel 074)
  Work number: ubmu0062_065_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 308
  Lecture: The composer's uses of modern technology, part V
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 66, December 9, 1969, 1969-12-09, 1 10 inch reel; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_066_01.wav, ubmu0062_066_02.wav (Box 6, Reel 075)
  Work number: ubmu0062_066_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 309
  Anhalt, István
  Lecture: Your voice, my voice, her voice, their voices …Vo(I)
  Performers: István Anhalt, lecturer
  Note: Program inserted in container. Water damaged and reel over-full.
  Work number: ubmu0062_066_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 310
  Cento (1967)
  Duration: 8:01
  Note: Check to see if it was recorded
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 67, November 11, 1970, 1970-11-11, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_067_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_067_01_02.wav, ubmu0062_067_02_01.wav, ubmu0062_067_02_02.wav (Box 6, Reel 076-077)
  Work number: ubmu0062_067_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 311
  Nabokov, Nicolas, 1903-1978
  Lecture: Rasputin, myth, mystery, history, music
  Performers: Nicolas Nabokov, lecturer
  Note: Note inserted in container.
  Work number: ubmu0062_067_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 312
  The holy devil. Excerpts
  Duration: 31:01
  Note: Note inserted in container. Check to see if this was recorded - it looks like a cassette exists.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 68, December 2, 1970, 1970-12-02, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_068_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_068_01_02.wav, ubmu0062_068_02_01.wav (Box 6, Reel 078-079)
  Work number: ubmu0062_068_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 313
  Lecture: Symbolism in music
  Note: Index card inserted: "Spoken portion of lecture"
  Work number: ubmu0062_068_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 314
  Symboli chrestiani (1956)
  Duration: 18:34
  Note: Index card in container: "Music portion of lecture"
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 69, November 20, 1972, 1972-11-20, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_069_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_069_01_02.wav, ubmu0062_069_02.wav (Box 6, Reel 080-081)
  Work number: ubmu0062_069_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 317
  Feldman, Morton, 1926-1987
  Swallows of Salangan (1961)
  Duration: 5:17
  Note: Program inserted in container.
  Work number: ubmu0062_069_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 318
  False relationships and the extended ending (1968)
  Performers: William Appleby, Stephen Manes, James Whitman, pianos; Henry Rubin, violin; David Gibson, violoncello; Unnamed performer, trombone; Jan Williams, chimes
  Duration: 21:24
  Work number: ubmu0062_069_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 316
  Two pianos (1957)
  Performers: Morton Feldman, William Appleby, pianos
  Duration: 9:03
  Work number: ubmu0062_069_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 315
  Performers: Morton Feldman, lecturer
  Work number: ubmu0062_069_05
  Original cassette number: SLR 319
  Lecture: Morton Feldman answers questions from the audience.
  Note: Program inserted in container. Discussion probably starts on Reel 078.
- Slee Lecture Recital no. 70, February 2, 1973, 1973-02-02, 2 10 inch reels; Baird Recital Hall Preservation files: ubmu0062_070_01_01.wav, ubmu0062_070_02_01.wav (Box 6, Reel 082-083)
  Work number: ubmu0062_070_01
  Original cassette number: SLR 320
  Work number: ubmu0062_070_02
  Original cassette number: SLR 321
  Madame Press died last week at ninety (1971)
  Duration: 5:09
  Work number: ubmu0062_070_03
  Original cassette number: SLR 322
  Viola in my life I
  Performers: Eiko Ito, flute; Henry Rubin, violin; Jesse Levine, viola; David Gibson, violoncello; Richard Trythall, piano; Dennis Kahle, percussion; Jan Williams, conductor
  Duration: 14:42
  Work number: ubmu0062_070_04
  Original cassette number: SLR 323
  Viola in my life II